Take a second now, and listen to what you can hear around you.
现在花点时间，听听你周围能听到什么。
Your breathing?
你的呼吸声？
Traffic?
交通声？
Silence?
还是寂静？
If it's the last of those, then good news because silence offers significant benefits for our minds and bodies.
如果是最后一种，那是个好消息，因为寂静对我们的身心有着显著的好处。
In our noise-filled world, silence can make us feel calmer mentally.
在我们充满噪音的世界里，寂静能让我们在精神上感到更平静。
The absence of noise gives the brain more time to process information and therefore provides much-needed mental clarity.
没有噪音能让大脑有更多时间处理信息，从而提供我们急需的清晰思路。
Your focus can improve, and you could feel a deeper connection to emotions and thoughts when there is reduced background noise, according to Pysch Central article 'The hidden benefits of silence'.
根据《寂静的潜在好处》一文，当背景噪音减少时，你的注意力可以提高，并且你能感受到与情绪和思维更深的连接。
There have been a variety of studies proving that silence can reduce stress levels.
已有大量研究证明，寂静可以降低压力水平。
Silence achieves this by lowering cortisol and adrenaline, which encourages mindfulness, promotes self-awareness, and allows the brain to 'reset' and gives a peaceful break from busy lives.
寂静通过降低皮质醇和肾上腺素来实现这一点，这能促进专注力，增强自我意识，让大脑"重启"，远离忙碌的生活，获得短暂的平静。
There are physical benefits too.
寂静也有身体上的好处。
A 2013 study called 'Is silence golden?' found that silence can increase the number of cells in the hippocampus of the brain.
2013年一项名为《寂静是金吗？》的研究发现，寂静可以增加大脑海马体中的细胞数量。
Researchers studied mice and found that just two hours of silence a day led to cell development.
研究人员对老鼠进行了研究，发现每天仅仅两小时的寂静就能促进细胞发育。
A study into the effects of music and silence was conducted by The National Institutes of Health.
美国国立卫生研究院进行了一项关于音乐和寂静效果的研究。
Researchers interspersed different musical styles with a period of two-minute silence and discovered that when this silence was introduced, the participants' 'respiratory frequency, heart rate, and blood pressure all decreased to below baseline levels'.
研究人员将不同的音乐风格与两分钟的静默期交替进行，发现当引入这种静默时，参与者的"呼吸频率、心率和血压都降低到了基线水平以下"。
While silence has proven mental and physical benefits, did you know it can also help you in conversation?
虽然寂静已被证明对身心有益，但你知道吗，它还能在对话中帮助你？
On the BBC podcast 'The glories of being quiet', the presenters discussed how silence in conversation means you're able to listen more and give others the chance to share what they need to.
在BBC播客《安静的荣耀》中，主持人讨论了对话中的寂静意味着你能更多地倾听，并给别人表达自己的机会。
This will naturally make you a better conversational partner and can help nurture relationships.
这自然会让你成为一个更好的谈话伙伴，并有助于培养人际关系。
Plus, it helps you to listen and respond in a calm and confident way.
此外，它还能帮助你以冷静自信的方式倾听和回应。
So, turn down the noise and relax into some silent peace.
所以，关掉噪音，放松进入一片宁静的平和吧。